<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.9.5" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.9.5" modifiedDate="2025-09-25T00:22:48"><properties><titles><title>Long did I toil</title><title>359</title></titles><verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder><authors><author>His Servant</author></authors><songbooks><songbook name="Christ in Song" entry="359" /></songbooks></properties><lyrics><verse name="v1"><lines>{lang-eng}Long did I toil, and knew no earthly rest;
Far did I rove, and found no certain home;
At last I sought them in His sheltering breast,
Who opes His arms, and bids the weary come.
With Him I found a home, a rest divine;
And I since then am His, and He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse><verse name="v2"><lines>{lang-eng}Yes, He is mine! and naught of earthly things,
Not all the charms of pleasure, wealth or power,
The fame of heroes, or the pomp of kings,
Could tempt me to forgo His love an hour.
Go, worthless world, I Cry, with all that’s thine!
Go! I my Savior’s arm, and He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse><verse name="v3"><lines>{lang-eng}The good I have is from His stores supplied,
The ill is only what He deems the best.
He for my Friend, I’m rich with naught beside;
And poor without Him, though of all possessed.
Changes may come—I take, or I resign,
Content, while I am His, while He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse><verse name="v4"><lines>{lang-eng}Whate’er may change, in Him no change is seen,
A glorious Sun that wanes not nor declines;
Above the clouds and storms He walks serene,
And on His people’s inward darkness shines:
All may depart—I fret not, nor repine,
While I my Savior’s am, while He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse><verse name="v5"><lines>{lang-eng}He stays me falling; lifts me up hen down;
Reclaims me wandering; guars from every foe;
Plants on my worthless brow the victor’s crown,
Which in return before His feet I throw,
Grieved that I cannot better grace His shrine,
Who deigns to own me His, as He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse><verse name="v6"><lines>{lang-eng}While here, alas! I know but half His love,
But half discern Him, and but half adore;
But when I meet Him in the realms above,
I hope to love Him better, praise Him more,
And feel, and tell, amid the choir divine,
How fully I am His, and He is mine.{/lang-eng}</lines></verse></lyrics></song>