<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedDate="2023-01-10T01:53:19">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Amazing Love how can it be</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>1997 Jeff M. Foote, Administered by Foote, Jeff M.</copyright>
    <ccliNo>2473888</ccliNo>
    <authors>
      <author>Charles Wesley</author>
      <author>Jeff M. Foote</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1a">
      <lines>E<br/>And can it be that I should gain<br/>An int'rest in the Savior's blood<br/>Died He for me who caused His pain<br/>For me who Him to death pursued</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1b">
      <lines>Amazing love how can it be<br/>That Thou my God shouldst die for me<br/>Amazing love! How can it be<br/>That Thou my God, shouldst die for me!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2a">
      <lines>'Tis mystery all! The Immortal dies!<br/>Who can explore His strange design?<br/>In vain the firstborn seraph tries<br/>To sound the depths of love Divine!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2b">
      <lines>'Tis mercy all! let earth adore<br/>Let angel minds inquire no more.<br/>Amazing love! How can it be<br/>That Thou my God, shouldst die for me!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3a">
      <lines>He left His Father's throne above<br/>So free so infinite His grace<br/>Emptied Himself of all but love<br/>And bled for Adam's helpless race</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3b">
      <lines>'Tis mercy all immense and free<br/>For O my God it found out me<br/>Amazing love! How can it be<br/>That Thou my God, shouldst die for me!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4a">
      <lines>Long my imprisoned spirit lay<br/>Fast bound in sin and nature's night<br/>Thine eye diffused a quickening ray<br/>I woke the dungeon flamed with light</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4b">
      <lines>My chains fell off my heart was free<br/>I rose went forth and followed Thee<br/>Amazing love! How can it be<br/>That Thou my God, shouldst die for me!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5a">
      <lines>No condemnation now I dread<br/>Jesus and all in Him is mine<br/>Alive in Him my living Head<br/>And clothed in righteousness Divine</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5b">
      <lines>Bold I approach the eternal throne<br/>And claim the crown through Christ my own<br/>Amazing love! How can it be<br/>That Thou my God, shouldst die for me!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
