<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedDate="2023-01-09T20:17:44">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>An Endless Supply</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>I've called on the Lord for the grace to be patient,<br/>The grace to forgive, and the grace to be strong;<br/>I've sought at His throne for the grace to be holy<br/>{When I have been tempted to stray and do wrong.} (3X)<br/>I've sought at His throne for the grace to be holy<br/>When I have been tempted to stray and do wrong.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>It seems that, for fullness, His grace is an ocean<br/>Without any bottom; without any shore.<br/>He never refuses His grace all sufficient,<br/>{No matter how often I come to His door!} (3X)<br/>He never refuses His grace all sufficient,<br/>No matter how often I come to His door!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>I've asked Him to open my eyes to see Jesus,<br/>Though, I have already beheld Him, in part.<br/>I long to see more of His infinite beauty;<br/>{I've prayed that the Lord would illumine my heart.} (3X)<br/>I long to see more of His infinite beauty;<br/>I've prayed that the Lord would illumine my heart.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Is there not an end to God's light or our vision?<br/>Is there not a limit to what can be shown?<br/>The more that we know of our wonderful Savior<br/>{The more of our Savior, there is to be known!} (3X)<br/>The more that we know of our wonderful Savior<br/>The more of our Savior, there is to be known!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>His wealth is not ever diminished by giving;<br/>Nor is He made poorer by granting a plea;<br/>The infinite stores of His riches in Jesus<br/>{Are never depleted by giving to me.} (3X)<br/>The infinite stores of His riches in Jesus<br/>Are never depleted by giving to me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>The sea would be smaller, less one drop of water;<br/>The universe dimmer, if one star should die;<br/>The spectrum reduced, if a soft hue was missing;<br/>{But, nothing can decrease an endless supply!} (3X)<br/>The spectrum reduced, if a soft hue was missing;<br/>But, nothing can decrease an endless supply!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
