<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.1" modifiedDate="2023-01-09T20:17:47">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>I Have a Friend, Whose Faithful Love*</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>I have a Friend, whose faithful love<br/>Is more than all the world to me<br/>'Tis higher than the heights above<br/>And deeper than the soundless sea<br/>So old, so new<br/>So strong, so true<br/>Before the earth received its frame<br/>He loved me - Blessed be His Name</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>He held the highest place above<br/>Adored by all the sons of flame<br/>Yet such His self-denying love<br/>He laid aside His crown and came<br/>To seek the lost<br/>And at the cost<br/>Of heavenly rank and earthly fame<br/>He sought me- Blessed be His name!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>It was a lonely place His trod<br/>From every human soul apart<br/>Known only to Himself and God<br/>Was all the grief that filled His heart<br/>Yet from the track<br/>He turned not back<br/>Till where i lay in want and shame<br/>He found me- Blessed be His name!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Then dawned at last that day of dread<br/>When desolate yet undismayed<br/>With wearied frame and thrown-crowned brow<br/>He, God-forsaken, man- betrayed<br/>Was then made sin<br/>on Calvary<br/>And, dying there in grief and shame<br/>He saved me- Blessed be His name!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Long as I live my song shall tell<br/>The wonders of His dying love<br/>And when at last I rise to dwell<br/>In the bright home prepared above<br/>My joy shall be<br/>His face to see<br/>And bowing there with loud acclaim<br/>I'll praise Him- Blessed be His name!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
