<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.9.5" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.9.5" modifiedDate="2022-08-22T13:11:09">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Jesus, my Lord, Thy nearness</title>
      <title>392</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>His Servant</author>
    </authors>
    <songbooks>
      <songbook name="Christ in Song" entry="392"/>
    </songbooks>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Jesus, my Lord, Thy nearness does impart
Sweet peace and gladness to the longing heart,
Thy gracious smile infuse a joyous thrill. 
And soul and body with sweet pleasure fill. 
And thankfulness.</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v2">
      <lines>We see not with our eyes Thy friendly face,
So full of kindness, love, and gentle grace
But in our hearts we know that Thou art here,
For Thou canst make us feel Thy presence near, 
Although unseen.</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v3">
      <lines>Whoever makes it life's chief aim and end
To have his happiness on Thee depend.
In him a well of joy for ever springs,
And all day long his heart is glad, and sings
Who is like Thee? </lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v4">
      <lines>To meet us ever with a friendly face, 
In mercy, patience, and the kindest grace,
Daily Thy rich forgiveness to bestow.
To comfort, heal, in peace to bid us go,
Is Thy delight.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Lord, for Thy rich salvation, hear our prayer.
And daily give us an abounding share;
And let our souls, in all their poverty.
From deep-felt love be looking unto Thee
Till life's last end.</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v6">
      <lines>In sorrowing hours may our o'erflowing eyes
For comfort look to Thy dear sacrifice;
And, with Thy cross before us, may we find 
Thy genuine image stamped upon our mind,
In constant view!</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v7">
      <lines>Lord, at all times mayst Thou within us find
A loving spirit and a childlike mind;
And from Thy wounds may we receive the power,
Through all life's weal and woe, in every hour,
To cling to Thee.</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v8">
      <lines>Thus, till the heavens receive us, shall we be
Like children, finding all our joys in Thee;
And though the tears of sorrow oft must fall, 
Yet, if Thou to our hearts art All in All,
Sweet peace will come.</lines>
    </verse>
	<verse name="v9">
      <lines>Thy wounded hand, dear Saviour, as a friend. 
Thou dost to us in faithfulness extend;
At the sad sight our tears of grief must flow,
And conscious shame come o'er us as we go.
With thankful praise.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>